So we've covered steps 1 to 4 of the five step strategy.
というわけで､ 5つのステップのうち､ ステップ1から4までを説明した｡
And that brings us to step five, which is productionize the one that maybe you haven't thought as much
そして､ ステップ5､ つまり､ これまであまり考えていなかったかもしれないが､ プロダクション化だ｡
And this is about saying we built our model.
そしてこれは､ 私たちがモデルを構築したと言うことだ｡
It's time for prime time.
プライムタイムの時間だ｡
We typically will start by defining an API that can be used to call our model to call our code.
私たちは通常､ コードを呼び出すためにモデルを呼び出すのに使えるAPIを定義することから始める｡
That itself is either using a open source model or making a call to a frontier model with with various
それ自体は､ オープンソースのモデルを使うか､ ラグやプロンプト・エンジニアリングのような様々な足場を持つフロンティア・モデルを呼び出すかのどちらかだ｡
We then decide how are we going to host and deploy our model, our API.
そして､ 我々のモデルやAPIをどのようにホストし､ デプロイするかを決める｡
We address things like how it's going to be monitored, the information security concerns, how will
どのように監視するのか､ 情報セキュリティーへの懸念､ どのように規模を拡大するのか､
it scale up?
などだ｡
We then measure the business metrics that we had identified all the way back in step one and continuously
そして､ ステップ1で特定したビジネス指標を測定し､ 継続的に再訓練を行い､
retrain, measure performance, and improve our model on an ongoing basis.
パフォーマンスを測定し､ モデルを改善していく｡
These are all part of the Productionize activity.
これらはすべてプロダクショナイズの活動の一部である｡
And so with that, where are we in our business problem that we've taken on to predict product prices.
というわけで､ 製品価格を予測するために私たちが取り組んでいるビジネス上の問題とは､ どのようなものなのでしょうか？
So the first step understand we've done it.
だから､ 最初の一歩は理解できた｡
We understood it.
私たちはそれを理解していた｡
We've talked about metrics.
メトリクスの話はした｡
We know what we've got to do.
やるべきことは分かっている｡
Preparation is what we're doing right now.
今やっているのは準備だ｡
We are in the middle of preparing our data set.
データセットを準備している最中だ｡
And then we need to select our model or models.
そして､ モデルを選択する必要がある｡
We need to customize.
カスタマイズが必要だ｡
And then finally we need to productionize.
そして最後にプロダクション化する必要がある｡
So we will be going through all of those steps.
だから私たちは､ そのすべてのステップを踏むことになる｡
But we will be first of all finishing the second step preparation.
しかし､ まずは第2段階の準備を終える｡
And with that let's go right now back to JupyterLab and get to preparing.
それではJupyterLabに戻って準備に取り掛かりましょう｡